usmobile.com 2017-11-30

# Privacy Policy | US Mobile

###### Oh no, your cart is empty

There’s only one thing you can do. Start adding items!

* * *

###### We care about your privacy

We make the security and confidentiality of the personal information that you provide to us a high priority. We understand the trust that you give us when you provide information to us.   
Our Privacy policy help you make informed decisions when using our website. Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you, businesses, consumers and the general public in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us, and to help you make informed decisions when using our web site and all of our related services there-in.

###### Personal information

This policy applies to personally identifiable information ("personal information"), which is information that we directly associate with a specific person or entity (for example, name; addresses; telephone numbers; usernames and passwords; call records; wireless device location). Personal information does not include "anonymous" or "aggregate: information neither of which are associated with a specific person or entity.

###### Collection of personal information

We collect personal information about you when you use our services or otherwise interact with us. Such information includes:   
Information you provide. We collect personal information when you sign up for and use our services, and when you e-mail, call, or otherwise communicate with us. For example, we may collect personal contact, billing, and credit information when you sign up for voice or purchase other products or services. We may also collect personal information when you call, chat, or e-mail our customer service representatives, enter information on our Web sites, submit survey responses or pay for service. If you provide personal information to us in connection with a co-sponsored Web site, this policy will apply to our use of the information and the co-sponsor's policy will apply to their use of the information.   
Information automatically collected due to use of our wireless services. We collect information about our wireless services that you use, including network traffic data, call records, websites visited, applications and features used, service options chosen, mobile and device number(s) and other similar information. We collect and use data regarding your mobile device location for a variety of purposes as described below. We also automatically collect certain information, which may be associated with personal information, whenever you use our services or Web sites. We may also obtain personal information about you from other sources. For example, we may receive your contact information, demographic information and updated address information from our shippers or other vendors. If you access third party services, such as social media services, through our Web sites, we also may collect information such as your user name, password, and other information made available to us through those third party services. Finally, we also may collect information about your online activity, such as content viewed and pages visited. We collect this automatic information to help us understand the interests of our community members and visitors and customize your user experience, among other things.

###### Use of personal information

We use personal information for a variety of business purposes, including for example, to complete transactions and bill for products and services; verify your identity; respond to your requests for service or assistance; anticipate and resolve actual and potential problems with our products and services; create and improve products and services; suggest additional or different products or services; collect for our services; make internal business decisions about current and future offers; provide personalized service and user experiences; protect our rights and property; and contact you about other services offered by US Mobile. We may disclose personal information to personnel employed by our company or affiliated companies in order to further any business purposes, including those described in this policy.

###### Disclosure of personal information

Other than as described below, we do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personal information without your consent, to unaffiliated third-parties to market their services or products to you:   
With your consent. We may disclose personal information about you to third-parties with your consent. We may obtain your consent in several ways, such as in writing; online, through "click-through" agreements; orally, including through interactive voice response; or when your consent is part of this policy or the terms and conditions pursuant to which we provide you service. Your consent is sometimes implicit. For example, if you purchase a product and ask that it be shipped to your home, you implicitly consent to our disclosure of your name and address to a third-party shipping company to complete delivery.   
To the primary account holder. We may disclose personal information of an account user to the primary account holder (the party financially responsible for the account). If a business, governmental agency, or other individual obtains service for you, that entity or individual is our customer, and we may provide personal information about you or your use of the service to them or others at the direction of the account holder. When you are the primary account holder, but you receive special or discounted pricing, terms, or other benefits through another party's agreement with us (for example, an employee discount), we may provide enough personal information to that party to verify your initial and continuing eligibility for benefits under their agreement with us and to calculate any associated discounts.   
Third-parties Performing Services on Our Behalf; Transaction Processing. We may disclose personal information to third-parties performing services on our behalf (for example, companies who complete transactions and perform credit checks, billing, credit and debit card payment processing, shipping, customer service, and marketing), or that perform transactions on your behalf (for example, verification of your account information at your request to some third-party business, processing of debit/credit card transactions), or transfers related to your service (for example, number portability). Your wireless telephone number, the numbers you dial, and other information about your usage will be available to companies that perform underlying telecommunications services on our behalf to facilitate the origination, transport and termination of your US Mobile calls.   
Third-party services: Your personal information may be disclosed when the use of our services allow you to take advantage of services and products offered by other companies. For example, if you are roaming on the network of another carrier, your wireless telephone number, the numbers you dial, and other information about your usage will be available to that carrier to facilitate that service.   
Business transfers: We may disclose personal information as part of a corporate business transaction, such as a merger or acquisition, joint venture, corporate reorganization, financing, or sale of company assets, or in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, in which personal information could be transferred to third-parties as a business asset in the transaction.   
Legal process & protection of US Mobile and others. We may disclose personal information or communications where we believe in good faith such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law or respond to legal process (for example, lawful subpoena, court order, E-9-1-1 information); to enforce or apply agreements, the Terms and Conditions or this policy; to initiate, render, bill, and collect for services and products; to protect our rights or property; in connection with claims, disputes, or litigation; to protect users of our services and other carriers or providers from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, or subscription to, such services; to facilitate or verify the appropriate calculation of taxes, fees, or other obligations due to a local, state, or federal government; or if we determine disclosure is necessary in an emergency situation.

###### Access to your information

You may access and modify your contact information by contacting us at www.usmobile.com or our Customer Service Department. We will make good faith efforts to resolve requests to correct inaccurate information except where the request is unreasonable, requires disproportionate technical effort or expense, jeopardizes the privacy of others, or would be impractical. You will not give, lend or otherwise disclose any passwords or other similar user identifications to any unauthorized person, or permit any unauthorized person to use your mobile device, account(s) or related passwords or user identifications. Any loss of control of passwords or other similar user identifications may result in the loss of control over your information. You will be responsible for any actions taken on your behalf or any person using your passwords or other similar user identifications. You must immediately change any passwords or other similar user identifications and notify us immediately if any passwords or other similar user identifications have been compromised.

###### Update and Revise Your Information

We take reasonable steps to ensure that your information is relevant, accurate, and complete. Your use of our services or our Web site may permit you to update or revise your personal information through our Web site or otherwise from time to time. If you remove certain information from your account(s), we only will retain those copies of such information as necessary for us to comply with governmental orders, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, enforce any agreement that you have entered into with us, and as we otherwise deem reasonably necessary.

###### Caller ID

When you use US Mobile services, your name and telephone number may be transmitted and displayed on the receiving party's communications device and/or phone bill.

###### Cookies

We may use cookies (small data text files placed on your computer or device) or similar technologies to identify the computer or device and record your preferences and other data so that our Web sites can personalize your visit(s). For example, if you register on our Web sites, we may use cookies to remember your registration information so you do not need to log into our Web sites each time you visit. We also may save your password in a cookie, if you checked the box entitled “Save this password for automatic sign-in” (or other similar words). Please note that we encrypt for security purposes customer IDs, passwords, and any other account-related data included in cookies. We may also use information collected from cookies to improve our sites, make recommendations, and complete transactions you request. You may be able to set your browser(s) to reject cookies or delete cookies, but that may result in the loss of some functionality on our sites. We may also use Web beacons (small invisible graphic images on a Web page or an HTML e-mail) to monitor interaction with our Web sites or e-mails. If we combine or link cookie or Web beacon information with personal information, we will treat the combined or linked information as personal information under this policy. We may employ third-parties to place advertisements about our products and services on other Web sites. The use of cookies, Web beacons, or similar technologies by such third-parties is subject to their privacy policies, not this policy.

###### Customer Proprietary Network Information (CPNI)

Customer Proprietary Network Information, CPNI, is a form of personal information that is generated in connection with the telecommunications services we provide to you. Specific federal laws and regulations protect CPNI. We are committed to full compliance with these federal laws and regulations in all respects. CPNI includes, for example, call details, call location information, and certain information about your rate plans and features. CPNI does not include your name, address, and phone number. Under federal law, you have a right, and we have a duty, to protect the confidentiality of CPNI and we have adopted policies and procedures designed to ensure compliance with those rules. We won't intentionally disclose your CPNI to third-parties without your permission, except as allowed under FCC rules, applicable law, or explained in this policy. We provide password protected online access to your account information through www.usmobile.com. For multi-line accounts, the primary account holder is authorized to access online account information for all the devices on the account.

###### Customer service monitoring

We may monitor and record phone calls, e-mails, chat, or other communications between you and our Customer Service representatives or other employees for training and quality assurance purposes and to review specific transaction requests.

###### Location Information

Our network may detect your device’s approximate location whenever it is turned on (subject to coverage limitations). This location technology makes the routing of wireless communications possible and is also the basis for providing enhanced emergency 9-1-1 service, which permits us to provide your general location to a public safety answering point, emergency medical service provider, or emergency dispatch provider. We may also use this technology to disclose, without a user's consent, the approximate location of a wireless device to a governmental entity or law enforcement authority when we are served with lawful process or reasonably believe there is an emergency involving risk of death or serious physical harm. We may also use your mobile device location to provide our wireless voice and data services, and location- based applications and services offered by us and third parties, including mapping, navigation, weather, mapping and other applications or tools. Wireless applications and services offered by us and third parties also use mobile device location data.

###### Protecting your information

We want you to feel confident about using US Mobile, and we commit to protecting the information we collect. While no company or Web sites can guarantee security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect the personal information you provide to us. For example, we permit only authorized personnel to access personal information, and they only may do so for permitted business functions. We also employ firewalls and intrusion detection systems to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your information that we maintain. However, we make no guarantee, representation or warranty that use of our services or Web sites is protected from all security threats, viruses, or other vulnerabilities or that your information always will be secure.

###### Protecting children’s privacy

The Web sites operated by US Mobile are general audience sites and do not offer services directed to children. Should an individual whom we know to be a child under age 13 send personal information to us, we will delete or destroy such information as soon as reasonably possible.

###### Visiting our web sites from outside the United States

If you visit our Web sites from outside the United States, your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and where we operate our databases. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. However, US Mobile takes steps pursuant to laws in the United States to protect your privacy. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.

###### Other governing terms

This policy does not modify or alter any applicable agreement you have with US Mobile. If you use or subscribe to our products and services, our US Mobile Terms of Service and certain other terms may apply to your use, purchase, or subscription. If this policy conflicts with any portion of those terms and agreements, those terms and agreements govern to the extent of the inconsistency.

###### Changes to this policy

We may update this policy if we materially change our practices or if legal or regulatory changes require it. If we decide to use or disclose personal information in a way that is materially different from that which was stated in this policy at the time the personal information was collected, we will notify you by either sending a notice to the email address you provide to us or by placing a prominent notice on our Web sites. You should refer to this policy often for the latest information and the effective date of any changes.

###### Log in to your account

##### Your details

Invalid Email or Phone # and/or Password 

* * *

###### Forgot password

To reset your account password, enter the email address you registered with and we'll send you a new one. 

Invalid Email or Phone# and/or Password 

* * *
